你去哪
Hey! Where are you going?
快把秘密告诉我 满足我的好奇心
Okay, let the cat out of the bag so my curiosity can kill it.
这两个人到底什么情况
What is going on with those two?
这是隐私问题 我全都告诉你
That's a personal matter. I'll tell you all about it!
庆功派对 庆功派对
Cast party! Cast party!
我们在办庆功派对
We are having a cast party!
-太好了  -他们都没买酒
- Yeah! - They didn't even buy alcohol!
只买了个迪斯科球灯和几条披风
Just a disco ball and some capes?
黑料
这就是全部了黑料
These are all the bad things you think you did?
黑料这就是全部了
黑料
-我发誓 我只能想出这么多  -这些都不是大新闻黑料
- I swear, this is all I can think of! - None of these are big stories!
黑料-我发誓 我只能想出这么多  -这些都不是大新闻
黑料
-我们都知道 肯定还有其他事  -老天啊黑料
- We all know there are more things. - Jesus Christ.
黑料-我们都知道 肯定还有其他事  -老天啊